I blink. I twitch. I jump. I click. I whistle. I shout.
I Swear is a drama, history film directed by Kirk Jones.
Diagnosed with Tourette Syndrome at 15, John Davidson navigates his way against the odds through troubled teenage years
and into adulthood, finding inspiration in the kindness of others to discover his true purpose in life.
John Davidson, played by Robert Aramayo.
Dottie Achenbach, played by Maxine Peake.
Heather Davidson, played by Shirley Henderson.
Tommy Trotter, played by Peter Mullan.
Young John Davidson, played by Scott Ellis Watson.
Shopkeeper, played by Sanjeev Kohli.
I Swear is a 2025 Scottish biographical drama film
directed, written, and produced by Kirk Jones.
It is based on the true life story of John Davidson, a Scottish man with severe Tourette's syndrome, and follows his life
primarily following the 1989 television documentary John's Not Mad, at a time when his condition was barely identifiable.
The film stars Robert Aramayo as Davidson, alongside Maxine Peake,
Shirley Henderson and Peter Mullan in supporting roles.
Scott Ellis Watson makes his acting debut as a young Davidson.
I Swear premiered at the 2025 Toronto International Film Festival on 7 September 2025,
and was released in the United Kingdom by StudioCanal on 10 October 2025.
The film explores themes of scotland, biography, based
on true story, tourette syndrome, 1980s.
The tone is emotional.